{"questions":[{"question":"Which of the following is responsible for sprint meeting?","level":"1","answers":["Scrum team","Scrum master","Product Owner","None of the above"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":2},{"question":"When acceptance testing is performed in Agile development?","level":"2","answers":["On request of customer","After system is ready","At the end of each iteration","Daily"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Select One Type of nonfunctional requirement?","level":"2","answers":["user requirements","product requirements","Efficiency requirements","2+3 is the two Correct Answers"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Which one of the following is not a step of requirement engineering?","level":"1","answers":["elicitation","design","analysis","documentation"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Types OF Reviews:","level":"3","answers":["Formal Reviews","Peer Reviews","The answers 1 & 2 are correct","There are no correct answers"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":3},{"question":"In Peer Review,the primary function is to use the skill of a group of people to","level":"3","answers":["identify needed improvements","certify correctness","encourage uniformity & enforce subjective rules","all of the above"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":1},{"question":"The UML was designed for describing:","level":"2","answers":["object-oriented systems","architectural design","SRS","Both object-oriented systems and Architectural design"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":4},{"question":"What's true about MVC?","level":"1","answers":["a Software Architecture�\u20AC�s Element","a software Application Architecture","a software Architecture patterns","There is no correct answer"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Software Maintenance includes","level":"3","answers":["Error corrections","Enhancements of capabilities","Deletion of obsolete capabilities","All of the mentioned"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":4},{"question":"What type of software testing is generally used in Software Maintenance?","level":"3","answers":["Regression Testing","System Testing","Black-box testing","White-box testing"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what is unit testing?","level":"2","answers":["is running the code","is testing a method by software developers","is to debuging all the code","is to testing all parts of a project"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":2},{"question":"What is the advantages of writing unit tests?","level":"2","answers":["Code maintainability as good unit tests enforces","Code testability","Design testability","all the above"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Software can be tested as :","level":"1","answers":["Black Box","White Box","answers one and two are correct","none of the mentioned"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Agile software engineering refers,","level":"3","answers":["A philosophy and a set of development guidelines","An active and continuous communication between developers and customers","Encourages customer satisfaction","All of the mentioned above"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":4},{"question":"________ specification is also known as SRS document","level":"1","answers":["white-box","grey-box","black-box","none of the mentioned"],"team":"Tiger","correct_ans":3}]}